Donguk Oh

Full-stack Developer / Windows App Developer

Calgary, Canada | okdonguk0@gmail.com | 403-471-0572

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/donguk-oh-2a1285200/ | GitHub: https://github.com/donoh5

Profile

Experienced Windows-based application development with 9 months of internship experience with a large ERP System company in South Korea. Extending myself as a web full stack developer, with MERN technology stack and SpringBoot framework. Strong at debugging and solving problems.

Skills

- .NET (C#)
- Spring boot (Java)
- Tailwind CSS
- MySQL
- Python

- React
- Node JS (JavaScript)
- MongoDB
- Oracle
- Azure

Work Experience

Software Developer

SysoIT - Seoul, South Korea

01/2022 - 09/2022

Successfully completed the project to convert the client's existing C++ program to C#.

- Communicated with two software developers and two DBAs, including myself, and developed 20+ menus
 out of 150+ menus with new technologies.
- Developed 150+ dialogs out of 210+ dialogs and more than 10% of speed improved on Excel functions.
- Continuously communicated with clients and developed 10+ new functions.
- Started without background knowledge of C++ and C# but handled tasks with strong searching and problem-solving capabilities.
- Applied independently developed model to sorting and styling charts, overall dialog structure, and data processing methods. Achieved a speed improvement of more than 30% without collisions with other functions.
- Maximized utilities provided by Devxpress. In case of Excel functions, removed different experiences
 due to version differences for each user.
- Converted 200+ database queries from Oracle to MySQL.
- More than 20% of speed improved in some database queries.

Technology used: .Net Framework (Winform), Devexpress, Oracle, MySql

Software Developer

Eyenix - Seoul, South Korea

05/2021 - 06/2021

Developed office-automation program using Python

- Automatically documenting attendance information through the existing attendance machine.
- Utilized Google Docs as a server.
- Developed to be used both online and locally.

Technology used: Python, Google Cloud & Docs API

Other Experiences

Calgary's Biggest Hackathon

07/2022

Participated in Hackathon for promoting Calgary's downtown and completed and demonstrated a small web service.

- Development was completed by constantly communicating with 10 team members for 48 hours.
- Developed a function to automatically post data from the web to Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, and e-mail immediately.
- Improved ability to solve problems faster.
- To complete the development in a short and limited time, learned how to communicate more effectively with the team.

Personal Projects

Portfolio In Progress

My portfolio starts with a little joke and consists of wood-tone themes that can create a relaxed atmosphere. I'll show who I am, what I can do, and what I've done.

- Using RestAPI with MongoDB and NodeJS.
- Deploying the Backend and Frontend apps using the Azure Web service.
- Reactive web app using TailWind CSS.
- Technology used: MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS)

Link: https://www.don5at.com/

DongSu In Progress

- Account book web service.
- Using RestAPI with MongoDB and NodeJS.
- Deploying the Backend and Frontend apps using the Azure Web service.
- Reactive web app using TailWind CSS.
- Technology used: MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS)

Paste It In Progress

- Enhance copy and paste function for Windows users.
- Continuously detect hotkeys in the background and handle them to work in any process.
- Provides the option to run automatically in the background when Windows starts.
- Technology used: WPF framework (C#)

Education

SAIT (Calgary, AB) / Software Development Diploma

May 2021 - December 2022